editorsweblog.org 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy - WAN-IFRA

### Data protection

WAN-IFRA is pleased that you have visited our website and are interested in our association, information, services and products. It is important to us to protect your personal data throughout the entire business process and we want you to feel secure when visiting our Internet pages. In the following, we explain what information WAN-IFRA collects when you visit our website and how this information is used.

### Personal data

Personal data is specific information about personal or factual characteristics relating to a certain natural person or a natural person who can be specified. This includes information such as your real name, address, telephone number and date of birth. Information which cannot be directly linked to your real identity - such as favourite websites or number of users of a site - is not considered personal data.

### Collection and processing of personal data

In normal cases, you can visit all publically accessible WAN-IFRA websites without providing any personal details.When you visit our web pages, our web servers always temporarily save for security purposes the connection data of the computer connecting to our site, a list of the web pages that you visit within our site, the date of your visit, the identification data of the type of browser and operation system used as well as the website through which you linked to our site. Personal information such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address is not collected unless you provide this data voluntarily, e.g. as part of a registration for an event, competition, survey, fulfilment of a contract, or an information request.

### Utilisation and sharing of personal data

WAN-IFRA consists of the headquarters operation in Frankfurt (Germany), a headquarters extension in Paris (France) as well as subsidiaries outside of the EU in Singapore and Chennai (India). The data recorded by the local WAN-IFRA regional offices is stored and managed on central database servers at the headquarters in Frankfurt. However, the subsequent processing steps may be carried out at the individual WAN-IFRA offices worldwide as required.

When the regional offices access personal data stored on the central server in Frankfurt, it is considered a transfer to 3rd parties. In the case of France, this is done in accordance with the laws and directives of the EU as well as the complementary local regulations. Although outside of the European Union, the offices in Singapore and India have been bound by directive to abide by the EU data protection laws.

WAN-IFRA does not share, sell, transfer or otherwise disseminate your personal data to other third parties, unless this is required for the purpose of the contract, is required by law or you have given express consent to do so. For instance, it may be necessary to pass on your address and order data to our contractors when you order products or services.

### Information from WAN-IFRA

WAN-IFRA companies would like to contact you in order to inform you about our offers and other news. When registering on our web pages, your data is stored initially in the central WAN-IFRA address database. This enables us to send you e-mails as well as postal communications.

If you do not wish these services, you have several options to have your data removed from the distribution list. We will process any such request addressed in writing to our Customer Service Department as quickly as possible.

You determine whether you wish to continue to receive services offered via e-mail. Every user can select which services he or she wishes to receive in the future by means of the "Unsubscribe – Manage Profile" button.

Of course, as a WAN-IFRA customer you will continue to receive all necessary information concerning important changes in connection with existing contracts (e.g. confirmations, cancellations, etc.).

### Use of web tracking

We use tracking software to determine how many users visit our website and how often. We do not use this software to collect personal data. The data are used solely in anonymous and summarised form for statistical purposes and for developing the website.

### Use of cookies

"Cookies" are small files that enables us to store information related to your PC and you, the user, specifically, while you visit one of our websites. Cookies help us to determine how frequently our internet pages are accessed as well as the number of users. And they help us configure our offers so that they are as convenient and efficient as possible for you.

We use so-called "session cookies", those that are stored exclusively for the duration of your visit to one of our Internet pages. We do not create an individual profile of your online activities.

Using our products and services without cookies is also possible. In your browser, you can deactivate the saving of cookies, limit them to particular websites, or set the browser to notify you when a cookie is sent. You can also delete cookies from your PC hard drive at any time (file: "cookies"). Please note that in this case you will have to expect a limited page presentation and limited user guidance.

### Security

WAN-IFRA takes the necessary technical and organisational security measures to protect your personal data from being lost or misused. Thus your data is saved in a secure operating environment which is not accessible to the public. In certain cases, your personal data is encrypted by Secure Socket Layer technology (SSL) during transmission. This means that an approved encryption procedure is used for communication between your computer and the WAN-IFRA servers if your browser supports SSL.

### Right to information and revocation

Upon written request, we will inform you as to what personal data we have stored pertaining to you. In accordance with the Telemedia Act, you have the right as a user to obtain information about what data WAN-IFRA has stored relating to your person.

You may, at any time, revoke previously given permission to store, process, or use your personal information. In such a case, WAN-IFRA will block or delete your data in accordance with your wishes.

### Links to other websites

WAN-IFRA websites contain links to other websites. WAN-IFRA has no influence on the editorial content of third party websites, nor whether their operators respect data protection regulations.

### Contact

If you have any queries concerning the processing of your personal data, kindly contact the WAN-IFRA Data Protection Officer who will be pleased to assist you with all requests for information, proposals or complaints.

Data Protection Officer  
WAN-IFRA (CH)  
Rotfeder-Ring 11  
60327 Frankfurt am Main, Germany
